Thank you for watching
ME
33rd single hit key
Inoue, who is playing the center for the first time, went to his hometown by himself for this hit period.
While touring the places of his memories, he will campaign the new song to thank his friends and 33 people who have helped him.
And as a way to thank them for all they've done for us, we're going to have them campaign for our new song. 33 people.
I can't think of 33 people.
Last time I visited, I thanked all my colleagues and teachers in the payroll department.
Next, I went to a Chinese restaurant that I've frequented with other members of the payroll department.
Here, I talked about my homeroom teacher who was a big help to me... but she had some business today...
I graduated from another high school, and at the graduation ceremony I received a diploma, but at that time, Inoue-san said she had one more letter for me.
My homeroom teacher sent me letters from all the teachers I had worked with, so it wasn't just my graduation certificate.
I didn't graduate from that high school, but it made me happy.
She was a very kind and helpful teacher, and I was very happy to have her as my homeroom teacher.
Here, homeroom teacher Ms. Ishii made a surprise appearance, and Inoue expressed his gratitude to her via video call.
I remember the letter and the message I received at the graduation ceremony at my new school.
I still have a very precious photo of it.
Thank you very much. I'm very happy to see this message, because it made me feel like I'll do my best.
If that's the case, it was worth it.
I'm so glad I sent it to you. I'm glad I did.
I couldn't properly express my gratitude to Mr. Ishii, so thank you very much again.
No, no, it's the same to you, Inoue-san, for taking on the challenge... and being active outside the school.
I think there are a lot of people who are encouraged by your challenge, including me and other teachers and friends.
So I really want to say thank you to you, Inoue-san.
Thank you very much. I'm very happy.
I'm also going to report to my homeroom teacher that I've become the center and promote my new song.
I'm going to pre-order the CD, so please do your best. I know you have a lot of hard work ahead of you, but I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I'm coming to eat.
In addition, I'm going to make a campaign to my favorite restaurant, and I'm not going to eat one of your snacks.
I didn't eat one of your pastries.
I did eat it, but...
Yuigahama.
Yuigahama was the place to hang out with friends about 90% of the time.
So I used to go to Yuigahama a lot.
Yuigahama, but we didn't really go in the ocean.Yuigahama, but we didn't really go in the water.
We just talked in the ocean for three or four hours.
It's nice, but it's very humid.
We just sat around here where it wasn't wet.
We were just sitting here on the beach looking at the ocean and talking the whole time.
I didn't have sunscreen on.
I didn't wear sunscreen, so I was black when I first joined.
It's better now.
It's amazing.
It's been a long time.
Who's that?
I'm a friend who used to come here a lot.
So now my best friend from elementary school is in Gaugier.
I'll let him tell you about his memories of the two of you.
I asked him if he would be my friend when we were in elementary school. Something like that.
I think he asked me.
We met, and we were in class together at 11.
He was feeding me so much.
He was.
I brought fruit every day.
Akari would always get one.
It was so cute how she reacted.
You sure? Thank you! Delicious!
It makes me want to remember.
I think the attraction started back then.
Thank you for the compliment in front of the camera.
She's the kind of girl who gives you a chance to do things.
I thought if I didn't try to get involved with people, I wouldn't talk.
Akari, you talk all the time.
She tells me about things like this.
"This is something I like," or "This is my hobby.
or "This is something I like" or "This is my hobby.
Akari gives me a lot of information.
That's how I became the kind of person I am today.
Thank you very much.
I would like to once again campaign for a new song for my best friend who has been such a great help to me.Campaign for a new song again for such a good friend of mine who has been such a great help to me.
Thank you for everything.
Keep up the good work.
I'm rooting for you.
I always feel that Akari...
It's not good that Akari went away to school, is it?
Isn't this where it starts to get bad?
Komakura.
Komachi-dori is the place to be.
All the girls who live around here come to Komachi Dori.
I used to come here too.
I used to come here for school events.
I used to eat apple pie all the time.
It's a little closed.
But it's closed a lot.
And honey.
What a surprise.
A bonus
extra
extra!
Cheese
I think someone's coming up with a bit of a memory.
It's been three years or something.
I kind of lost touch with him after high school.
I don't even have a contact number.
You scared me.
Thank you so much.
It's been a long time since I met my best friend from junior high school.
I wonder what he was like for Inoue.
When I started junior high school, I wanted to make friends with him.
We were seated next to each other at the beginning.
I tried my best to talk to him and he became my friend.
I did most of the adolescent things in junior high school with cheese.
I don't want to go after the festival.
Oh, I did! We went to eat shaved ice.
We did, didn't we?You ate.
Oh, I went! Shaved ice.
Me?
I spilled it.
You spilled it?
You were eating here.
I did.
You ate it on your lap.
Didn't you do something?
Mango?
Yeah.
I definitely had mango.
We were at karaoke and I was trying to drink juice while lying down.
I spilled so much.
I can't even remember.
Me?
I don't remember.
Here's to celebrate our reunion.
A task that will bring back memories for both of us to enjoy.
This looks delicious.
Careful with that.
I'll be careful.
Yes, it's good.
Maybe it's the mango. Shaved ice...
You're not alone at all.
Thank you very much.
They're all my friends.
I was so bad in school.
I'm really in the third grade.
I was in the first grade of middle school.
I had Nagi-chan circle them for me.
The only reason I got into high school was because of Nagi-chan.
If you hadn't invited me to cram school.
I probably wouldn't have gone to cram school.
And now I'm in college.So you're going to college now?
Yes, I'm going to college.
I'm studying to go to college.
If I hadn't committed all those sins.
I wouldn't have gone to college.
I'm really grateful.
That's great.
I didn't have my whole life ahead of me.
In middle school.
That's great.
I'm so happy for you.
You made it!
But I really...
I really wanted to have a best friend.
I wanted to have someone I could say, "This is my best friend.
I wanted to make one.
Someone I can hang out with.
I didn't have someone I could spend time with.
I didn't have anyone I could hang out with.
That's why, in my junior high school years.
I've been through a lot.
But we were together for three years.
Tork, you married me.
And that's the first thing.
I'm really grateful for that.
But now that we've lost touch...
I've lost touch with him.
That's why I'm glad to have this opportunity.
I'm so happy to have this opportunity.
I'm really happy.
I'm really...
Yeah, so I'll see you soon.
Please exchange contact information.
I'd really appreciate it.
I'm so happy to be your best friend again, and I'm so happy to be able to tell you
Reporting here at the center.Report centered here.
Thank you very much.
I'm standing right in the center.
If you can make it.
I'd like to take you to the restaurant where we made new memories.
To the restaurant where you made it all happen.
New Music Campaign
Thank you very much.
Nikagami is going to thank you, or rather...
It's a surprise and it just keeps coming up.
That's right.
And he came as a ghost from the haunted house.
And then he'll come back again.
It's a surprise, right?
And what are you giving away?
Single CDs?
Postcards.
Single CDs don't ring a bell.
If I'm giving away single CDs...
Why would I do that?
I'm sure you would.
He's the type to ask to be friends.
She's the type to ask to be friends.
That's right, that's right.
Friends are supposed to be something you dare to make.
I think so.
She seems like a strong person.
But a total klutz.
That's what I thought.
I guess I'm not quite ready for this side of the world.
I guess I'm not at my best yet.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm taking shelter from the rain, and I'm thinking about all the people who helped me.
I met some friends from school.
I went to cram school in junior high.I went to cram school when I was in middle school.
I've been working with the teachers at the cram school since I was in the third grade of elementary school.
I couldn't study very well.
I was not able to study very well, so I started cram school when I was in the 3rd or 4th grade of elementary school.
Thanks to that teacher, I managed to go to high school.
I was able to go to high school and keep up with my junior high school studies.
I remember how much he helped me.
It's been a long time.
We were just talking about the cram school.
When I say that episode, that person comes up.
It's the same system as when I come to the school.
I've been taking care of you for a really long time.
Even my mother still says to me.
If I hadn't gone to cram school or if I hadn't been a teacher
I wonder what you would have been
I'm not one of those kids who was such a handful for me
Yes.
I kept her busy, so even though she was busy, she was a hard worker.
I'd never heard her cry of weakness or vomit.
I mean, there were days when I just didn't feel like it.
It happened from time to time.
But in the third year of junior high school, when it came time to take the entrance exam...
Did I do my best?
I really can't do it.
That's the expression on your face.
When you don't understand something, you make a face like you don't understand it, and I'm grateful for that.
That's right, when she gets what I'm saying, and when she doesn't... it's a quick transition.
When he doesn't get it, he's in a daze.
That's when it's still there, like in the video.
I'm used to seeing that.
His expression hasn't changed.
It's that look.
That's when you don't understand.
I didn't know, and I first heard about it from the teachers around me, and of course I was surprised, and I didn't have so many corners of my mouth.
I didn't have the image of making everyone happy and joyful, so I was surprised.
At first, I was kind of worried about her, and I wondered if she was okay.At first, I'd look at you with a worried look and wonder if you'd be okay.
I wonder if I'm going to be able to speak well, and lately I've been thinking that maybe I'm ready.
You started it, didn't you? I wasn't really the type to be active in middle school.
To be honest, I was probably a little more aggressive in high school, but in a way I was making my high school debut.
So at first I wondered what the teachers who knew me in China would think.
But now I've been told that I can look at you with confidence, and I'm totally thrilled.
I'm really proud of you.
Inoue's presence has made the teacher rethink his educational policy.
Even now, I think that all the children I see have talents that we don't understand.
At the time, I didn't think I was this good.
I didn't think I was this good at it, or that I had the talent to do something in front of people that would please them so much.
It changed the way I looked at children.
Not because of their studies, but because of their various good qualities.
I have come to think that it would be better if they could work hard on their own.
Thank you very much.
And I would like to thank the teacher of the cram school who is my benefactor, and promote the new song
Thank you very much!
I look forward to working with you.
Good luck
I'll do my best, really.
We also handed the posters to the master and the waitresses at the restaurant where we were on location for the campaign.
The next memorable place was a karaoke bar that he used to go to when he was a student.
I really like to go to karaoke even when I'm alone.
but I didn't have a lot of money when I was a student.
I used to have free time with my friends to go to the karaoke bar.
We would get together at 10:00 in the morning and enter the karaoke bar at the same time the bar opened.
and go until 6 or 8 o'clock in the morning.
I would go all the way up to the max time.
But I guess most of them were in junior high and high school.
And then junior high school.
Oh, I'm an acquaintance.
I've been going there since I was about 17 years old.
For 17 years.
I'm Kaoru.
We've been friends for 17 years.
Inoue and I have known each other since we were 1 year old.Inoue and I have known each other since we were 1 year old.
Kaoru-san and I reminisced at our favorite karaoke bar.
This is so amazing.
We lived close to each other in the same apartment.
We played, we fought, we did all kinds of things.
When we were little, all we did was fight.
I think we even made out once because of that.
It's almost like that.
I don't know if I'm doing it all the time.
I used to make love quite often.
He's a good student.
But I'm also smart in the not-so-good way.
So when we do something bad together
And when they get mad at me, I just let them get away with it.
LOL.
When he was little, he was cute in his own way.
I remember when we were learning together.
Even if you were cute when you were little
But when you grow up, you become ugly.
That's amazing.
It woke me up.
I was like, "No, of course not.
I think I was having a hard time... and I think I was having a hard time then, too.
I remember that.
That's great.
Oh, that's great.
I think this is where I heard the most.
I think.
Most of the time I'm singing.
I listen to it all the time.
I guess most of them are anime songs and vocaloids.
The first one was definitely Cruel Angel.
Yes.
Do you remember it?
I'll definitely put it in there.I'll definitely put it in.
He compliments me on it.
I'm really good.
Are you singing?
No singing?
I never get compliments on my singing, and I bought some clothes.
He probably compliments me the most.
I don't know.
I don't know. Thanks for being my childhood friend.
But really, that's the biggest thing.
I have good friends from elementary school and middle school.
I feel safe with them.
I haven't seen her since she was 1 year old.
She's a little shy and a little tense, but...
But she never denies I've decided to do something.
She never laughs at anything I want to do.
Heh.
So that kind of thing is really important.
I can see why you've grown so much.
It's been like that since we were little.
If we hadn't grown up together.
I wouldn't have been able to appreciate it.
That's why I wanted to say thank you now.
I've probably had a lot of emotional support from you.
I wonder if I ever did.
It's good that you don't know. I want you to stay that way.
Now that I've expressed my gratitude, I'll have Inu Inu finish up with her usual course.
"The Cruel Tension Thesis.
That's good.
Good.
Wow. Those were the days.
I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a
Oh!
Wow!
Well, I feel like I'm back on the side I know better than I did on TV.Well, I was just thinking, I feel like I'm back on the side I know better than when I saw you on TV.
That's for sure.
The way she sang sounded so familiar, like she was Nagi.
I'm still thinking about the next song I'm going to put in!
The next memorable place was Mikawa Shrine near Hiratsuka City!
I've been coming to Mikawa Shrine every year with my family, and my parents since I was a little girl.
I've been coming here every year for the past 15 years for sure.
I used to draw fortunes, but I couldn't tie them when I was little.
No luck. I'm just out of luck.
I've used up all my antidotes. I drew a fortune when I took the high school entrance exam.
It was today. It said I'd fail the exam.
I was told I'd fail on the same day I went to see an ocular professional.
I just went to the eye doctor's office and he told me I'd fail. So I thought God's word was absolute.
I studied hard because I didn't want to fail.
I didn't want to fail, so I put in a lot of effort and managed to figure it out.
I decided to try fortune-telling to see if my new song would be a hit.
27, but my birthday is 17
27 is 20 if you add 10 to it
It's so close!
I'm counting on you!
That's it!
It's a medium lucky number!
If I could, I'd have gotten Shokichi
Nakayoshi well, well, well, well, well, well, well, it's all right, isn't it?
And I've been visiting Sagawa Shrine for more than 15 years, and I've been peering at the new song to Mr. Kannui at the shrine.
Wow, it feels so good! Thank you so much!
This is going to be a big hit!
[ED]
The light of the rain that shakes the earth and falls so hard
More eloquent than words
I can't look at the thunder and the wind
I don't care whose fault it is
I stepped on something important.
Apologizing won't make it go away.
I deserve to be punished.That's what you humans said.You humans told me to be careful.
Be careful.
We can't start over and make it.
The only thing we have to protect...
Someone to think of.
Love. Love.
Subtitle: Kiyo hiroiyo.
What do we do now?
Shall we run away from here
Or shall we spread out?
Oh, while no one knows
I'm committing some unforeseen sin